{
    "games": [
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "chien",
                    "content": [
                        "agneau",
                        "dog",
                        "canard",
                        "\u00e2ne"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "chat",
                    "content": [
                        "rat",
                        "ox",
                        "cat",
                        "agneau"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "cheval",
                    "content": [
                        "horse",
                        "singe",
                        "taureau",
                        "sheep"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "tigre",
                    "content": [
                        "tiger",
                        "rabbit",
                        "taureau",
                        "cow"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "mouton",
                    "content": [
                        "cow",
                        "sheep",
                        "taureau",
                        "pig"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "vache",
                    "content": [
                        "agneau",
                        "taureau",
                        "cat",
                        "cow"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "lapin",
                    "content": [
                        "cat",
                        "rabbit",
                        "taureau",
                        "dog"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "cochon",
                    "content": [
                        "rabbit",
                        "sheep",
                        "pig",
                        "agneau"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "boeuf",
                    "content": [
                        "singe",
                        "\u00e2ne",
                        "ox",
                        "agneau"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "lamb",
                    "content": [
                        "rabbit",
                        "rat",
                        "agneau",
                        "tiger"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "bull",
                    "content": [
                        "pig",
                        "sheep",
                        "canard",
                        "taureau"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "rat",
                    "content": [
                        "tiger",
                        "\u00e2ne",
                        "rabbit",
                        "rat"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "donkey",
                    "content": [
                        "taureau",
                        "singe",
                        "\u00e2ne",
                        "sheep"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "monkey",
                    "content": [
                        "dog",
                        "ox",
                        "pig",
                        "singe"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "duck",
                    "content": [
                        "horse",
                        "canard",
                        "tiger",
                        "dog"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}